

I'm a Welsh digital designer & illustrator based in Berkshire looking to expand my skills in UI design and web design in Berkshire, Oxfordshire, Bristol and South Wales. I create fantastic content for fantastic people, from pencil to pixel. I love to help people leap ahead.



hello@staceyjenkins.co.uk



www.staceyjenkins.co.uk

# How can I help?

Considerable experience at logo design, print design, illustration and web design with Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop CC, Illustrator CC and Indesign CC) and Affinity software.

Considerable experience with front-end web development with CSS, CSS3, jQuery, JS, RequireJS, HTML, HTML5, Jade/Pug, Bourbon Neat, Sass, SCSS, Susy and Compass (through Codekit), Github and Wordpress.

Also considerable experience in prototyping with Invision, email development and email image asset generation with Sketch, Adobe XD and Figma.

Intermediate experience with motion graphics and video editing with After Effects CC and Adobe Premiere CC and Final Cut Pro.

# **Employment**

### 2017 - 2020 ARTHAUS VISUAL COMMUNICATIONS LTD

#### **Graphic/Web Designer**

In-house web designer/graphic designer specialising in the production and design for online, interactive educational PDFs and online internal websites and portals. Designed five new internal websites of HSBC's own internal education platform and career development prospects.

#### **MMP GLOBAL**

#### AUG 2016 - NOV 2016

## Digital Designer/Artworker

Working as part of on-site account creating and amending existing brochures, letters, emails and marketing collateral for RAC. Pitched various technological improvements to improve workflows and created and coded HTML emails.

#### **SCREAMING FROG LTD**

## 2013 - 2016 Senior Digital Designer

Collaborated with a small team of SEO consultants to produce promotional infographics, editorial imagery, illustrations and interactive mini website content for the agency's clients, including MOO and Which?. Also managed the agency's brand visuals. Frequently engaged and negotiated with client and consultant design requests as well as initiating design processes which are now standard within the company.

#### **RM EDUCATION**

## 2011- 2012 Multimedia Designer

Delivered visual concepts for RM Education's products and services, including nationwide print material (flyers, posters, wall planners, print advertisements and product factsheets) and online material (websites, animations, online shop pages, questionnaires, web banners and interactives.) Corrected errors in existing online content and collaborated with fellow staff members with the creation of new online content. Also led a logo design workshop for Year 11 students.

# Education

UNIVERSITY OF WALES

#### 2006- 2009

**INSTITUTE, CARDIFF (UWIC)**BA (Hons) Graphic Communication

(2:1)

#### 2005 - 2006

# SWANSEA INSTITUTE OF HIGHER EDUCATION (SIHE)

Foundation in Art and Design, specialising in graphic communication (Merit)

#### 2003 - 2005

#### **GORSEINON TERTIARY COLLEGE**

4 A Levels: English Language [A], Graphic Design [A], Computing [B] and Media Studies [B]